https://blackperspective.com/privacy-statement/

Privacy Notice
This privacy notice discloses the privacy policies for JMR Publishing Enterprises (JMR) , Inc and all of its subsidiaries. This privacy notice applies solely to information collected by JMR. It will notify you of the following when required:
What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the website, how it is used and with whom it may be shared.
Information Collection, Use, and Sharing
We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone.
We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g. to ship an order.
Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy.
Your Access to and Control Over Information
You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address or phone number given on our website:
We request information from you on our order form. To buy from us, you must provide contact information (like name and shipping address) and financial information (like credit card number, expiration date). This information is used for billing purposes and to fill your orders. If we have trouble processing an order, we&#39;ll use this information to contact you.
We use &quot;cookies&quot; on this site. A cookie is a piece of data stored on a site visitor&#39;s hard drive to help us improve your access to our site and identify repeat visitors to our site. For instance, when we use a cookie to identify you, you would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site. Cookies can also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information on our site.
Some of our business partners may use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers). However, we have no access to or control over these cookies.
We partner with another party to provide specific services. When the user signs up for these services, we will share names, or other contact information that is necessary for the third party to provide these services. These parties are not allowed to use personally identifiable information except for the purpose of providing these services.
This website contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of any other site that collects personally identifiable information.
SUBMISSIONS WELCOME Submit an article to our website.
Add your event to our Job Fair Calendar.
Upload a job posting to our Career Search Engine
If you’d like to advertise with the Black Perspective, and to learn more about the benefits of minority recruiting, visit EqualityMagazines.com
GET INCLUDED IN INCLUSION The companies and organizations seen here are specifically hiring people with your talents, background, and skills.
Check out our job postings and list of participating employers to find your perfect career today.
OUR DIVERSITY FAMILY Visit our sister sites:
Copyright © 2019 The Black Perspective. All Rights Reserved.
